

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

ADDRESS
TOULOUSER ALLEE 17,
40211 DÜSSELDORF

PHONE +49 15736169809

EMAIL meydanipour.gelareh@gmail.com

## SOCIAL MEDIA

# LINKEDIN LINKEDIN.COM/Gelareh Lahijany

WEB PAGE:

<u>Team – Modellbasierte Entwicklung (uni-siegen.de)</u>

GITHUB PROFILE <a href="https://github.com/gelareh1985">https://github.com/gelareh1985</a>

# 文A LANGUAGE SKILLS:

ENGLISH: Fluent Persian: Native

German: A2

# Gelareh M. Lahijany

Software Developer / Data Scientist

Enthusiastic undergraduate PhD Research Assistant with 3+ years of experience in Software Development and working in the field, Model Driven Engineering with contribution of Graph Neural Network based Deep Learning techniques. Experienced in Data Science and creating input data models for a learning system using Deep Learning techniques.

#### **EDUCATION**

2018 - Now O PHD DEGREE

**University of Siegen, Germany:** Model Driven Engineering and Machine Learning, Undergraduate

2010 - 2015 O MASTER DEGREE

Azad University of Qazvin, Iran: Artificial Intelligence GPA: (17.17/20), (3.62/4)

2006 - 2009 O BACHELORES DEGREE

Azad University of Lahijan, Iran: Software Engineering GPA: (15.24/20), (3.25/4)

2002 - 2004 O ASSOCIATE DEGREE

University of Fouman, Iran: Software Engineering GPA: (15.30), (3.26/4)

2001 - 2002 O PREUNIVERSITY

Niki, Iran, Rasht: Mathematics and Physics GPA: (14.75/20), (3.15/4)

1998 - 2001 O HIGH SCHOOL

Mahde Danesh, Iran, Rasht: Mathematics and Physics GPA: (17.5/20), (3.67/4)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

PhD RESEARCH ASSISTANT in GERMANY 2018 - Now PhD Researcher: Working on a project related to Model Driven Engineering and Machine Learning using JAVA and PYTHON: (Libraries: Pandas, numpy, Matplotlib, NLTK, Skitlearn, Keras, Tensorflow) 2015 - 2018 SELF-EMPLOYED and INTERNSHIP in IRAN Part time freelance projects: Application Development with Android Studio, front-end (UI/UX Design). Working with JAVA and learning about Model Driven Software Development. Experience with Software Design Patterns 2013-2015 Software Engineer at IT department, Gohar Gil Adel company: Work experience in Programming (C#, VBA, Macros), Software Support and Maintenance 2010- 2015 MASTER OF SCIENCE Taking Courses including: image processing, statistical and structural pattern recognition, signal processing, fuzzy logic and evolutionary algorithms. Working on thesis entitled: Human Head Pose Estimation, and MATLAB. 2009 - 2010 GOHAR GIL ADEL in IRAN Internship at IT department, Gohar Gil Adel Company: Learning tasks related to software maintenance and support and hardware assembling.

#### **INTERESTS**

- Machine Learning
- Data mining
- Natural Language Processing
- Sentiment Analysis
- Data Analysis and Big Data
- Data Visualization

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Python and Java Programming
- Database Management System (SQL, neo4j)
- HTML, CSS, XML, JAVA SCRIPT
- Eclipse Modelling Framework
- Version Control System: Git, SVN
- Latex, Microsoft Office
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Inkscape

#### CERTIFICATES

- Machine Learning Certificate Stanford University (No Expiration date)
- Deep Learning Certificate IBM (No Expiration date)
- Python Programming Certificate Linkedin (No Expiration date)

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

#### Published

- [1] Rad, M.P., Badashian, A.S., Meydanipour, G., Delcheh, M.A., Alipour, M. and Afzali, H., 2009, June. A survey of cloud platforms and their future. In International Conference on Computational Science and its Applications (pp. 788-796). Springer, Berlin, Heidelberg.
- [2] Meydanipour, G. and Faez, K., 2013, September. Robust head pose estimation using contourletSD transform and GLCM. In 2013 8th Iranian Conference on Machine Vision and Image Processing (MVIP) (pp. 375-380). IEEE.
- [3] Meydanipour, G. and Faez, K., 2014, May. Head pose estimation using histogram of SIFT descriptors. In 2014 22nd Iranian Conference on Electrical Engineering (ICEE) (pp. 976-979). IEEE.
- [4] Aboozar, Gh. And Meydanipour, G., 2013, Gender Classification using Sparse Representation. In 8th Iranian Conference on Machine Vision and Image Processing (MVIP).

## Accepted: Under Publishment

[5] Meidanipour, G. Ohrndorf, M. Zenkert, J. Fathi, M. Kelter, U. Structural Bug Localization using Graph-based Deep Learning on UML Class Diagrams. In 2021 19th Conference on Software Engineering Research and Practice (SERP'21). Springer Nature Book.

#### Under Review

[6] Meidanipour, G. Ohrndorf, M. Zenkert, J. Fathi, M. Kelter, IdentiBug: Model-Driven Visualization of Bug Reports by Extracting Class Diagram Excerpts. In 2021 SMC. Systems, Man and Cybernetics Society. IEEE <a href="https://pi.informatik.uni-siegen.de/projects/identibug/smc21/index.html">https://pi.informatik.uni-siegen.de/projects/identibug/smc21/index.html</a>